I’m here to see Mr. Meacham.
You were right, George.
We have a traitor in the house.
There are five names on there.
Your wife’s one of them.
Why is that?
You asked me to
look at everyone.
I looked.
She has the security
clearance, she has the motive,
and she has the capability.
I had to put her down.
How long do you
think you’ll need?
Give me two weeks.
If Severus is
deployed as intended,
thousands of innocent
people will die.
Okay. One week.
If it is Kathryn, do you
really think you can do that?
How’s Anna?
Still mad.
- I’m sorry.
- I made a mistake, that’s all.
She just can’t let it go.
She will, eventually.
Yeah?
Some things really are
best swept under the rug.
I just wish it wasn’t
so fucking easy.
To cheat.
For us.
Mm.
Not everyone aspires to your
flagrant monogamy, George.
If you’d like Anna
to be less angry,
you might consider going home.
Good luck finding the rat.
I can feel when
you’re watching me.
Sorry.
I like it.
I understand this is not
the casual dinner you’d prefer.
Yeah. It’s an unusual group.
Data scraper, two agents
and the in-house shrink.
What are we hunting this time?
Severus.
And you think one
of them took it?
Possibly.
Hmm.
It’s been a while since we
had a traitor to dinner.
At least knowingly.
We shouldn’t be discussing this.
No, probably not.
I would’ve thought you’d
start with polygraphs.
I wanted to try something
more elegant first.
What’s on the menu?
Fun and games.
Will there be a
mess to clean up?
With any luck.
- They suit you.
- Mm.
No, you spent too much.
It’s boring how much
you think about money.
It’s terrifying
how much you don’t.
Avoid the chana masala.
Contains a healthy
amount of DZM 5.
Darling, you may
not dose our guests.
One of them is a liar.
I want to know which.
♪ I never thought
it would happen ♪
♪ With me and the
girl from Clapham ♪
♪ Out on the windy common ♪
♪ That night I ain’t forgotten ♪
♪ When she dealt
out the rations ♪
♪ With some or
other passions... ♪
- Matthew.
- Hello, sir.
I want to settle up for
the table by the door.
- Of course.
- And I’ll have a double Jameson.
Straightaway, sir.
I know they’re not that
much older, really,
but I kind of feel like I’m
going to my parents’ house.
If-if they weren’t divorced
and didn’t hate each other.
Well, here’s what I know.
You don’t get invited
to dinner twice
if you say no the first time.
But why now?
With 24 hours’ notice?
And why us?
We all work together.
Two couples in the same field.
It’s not that much of a reach.
So you believe this
was just spontaneous?
I’m assuming so until I see
reason to believe otherwise.
You and Freddie sitting
across from each other
after what just happened?
That could be read
as provocative.
Freddie’s fine.
Right?
How should I know?
Ask the shrink.
Whose idea was it, do you think?
- George or Kathryn?
- STOKES and CLARISSA: George.
- Sorry, sorry. So sorry.
- For fuck’s sake, Freddie.
I mean, you booked the table.
You’re the one that
wanted to meet beforehand.
I am absolutely at
fault, I admit it.
And Dr. Vaughan, were
she allowed to say so,
would claim there’s
a certain hostility
in my chronic tardiness.
But in order to make
it up to you all,
I have paid the bill and
tipped like a gangster.
Oh, come on.
We are celebrating
James’s well-deserved,
meteoric ascent
through the ranks.
Cheers.
- Shall we?
- Right.
Wait.
I was hoping for some pointers.
I mean, how shall I behave?
Praise his cooking, and I
promise all will be magical.
- Hello.
- Kathryn.
- On time and everything.
- Come in.
- Thank you.
Oh, shall I take that?
No, I’ll take it to the kitchen.
Come in. Yes, it’s
cold, isn’t it?
Hello.
- Lovely to see you.
- All right.
- I should take your coat.
- Wow.
Thank you.
This is, um... beautiful.
Oh, yeah.
The joys of not
having children, hey?
- What would you like to drink?
- Rum.
- Mmm.
- ’98 for the table.
- Right.
Oh, yes, lovely.
Should we get this over with?
I get it, why you went with him.
- Yes?
- James is the smart play.
Young, aggressive and...
How shall we say it?
Uncompromised.
I’d always hoped
it would be you.
I drink too much,
I fuck too much,
and I owe more than I’m worth.
The pills are becoming
a problem as well.
I’m so glad I can
confide in you, George.
I need to change.
Oh, give them a break.
Most of NCSC is 25-year-olds.
They were just mucking around,
trying to zero-day
a central router.
They didn’t know they’d
brick the whole system.
Wait. Syria 2012?
That was you?
- That was us?
- I don’t know.
I don’t work on that
side of the house.
That op was tight.
I’ve read that string.
It’s a very sexy piece of code.
Mm. It was all fine till
little Eddie Snowden
decided to call everybody
out, said it was a fuckup.
It shut Assad’s ass
right down, didn’t it?
How many civilians
died as a result?
Greater good.
Yeah, I don’t find
amorality attractive.
Then give up either your
profession or your sex life.
I give it two weeks.
Optimistic.
Did you get hell from oversight?
- Nothing I couldn’t handle.
- Oh, please.
The committee fucked with
Kathryn exactly once.
Half of them lost
their assignments.
’Cause that’s what
bad bitches do.
Chana masala is
fantastic, by the way.
Absolutely delicious.
- Mm.
- Thank you.
Come on.
Syria’s hardly the worst
thing we’ve ever done.
I once outed my kid’s
teacher as a pedophile
just to get him fired.
Oh.
Figures.
Turns out the guy’s
eight-year-old had a rash.
Guess he shouldn’t have
emailed those pictures.
That is uniquely
loathsome, Freddie.
You hand me an angle, I play it.
New teacher gave Matty an "A."
- Don’t fuck with SIS dad.
- So we’re all horrible people.
Is that what the point is here?
I prefer to say "complex."
And what’s wrong
with "patriotic"?
Come on, most of us
are sick as shit.
Nobody can lay a glove
on Oedipus over there.
What, you all don’t
know about that?
- Careful, Freddie.
- It’s common knowledge.
Well, that’s for him, not you.
It’s all right. But
thank you, darling.
See?
- George can handle it.
- Handle what?
Little Georgie surveilled
his own father.
Ouch.
Oh, my.
Well...
Daddy was an inveterate cheater.
Rarely if ever kept
it in his pants.
But he was senior
service, and he was,
shall we say, careful.
When half your life’s
in the black bag,
how’s little civilian wifey
ever gonna have a prayer
of knowing where
you’re sticking it?
- That’s crass.
- So was Thomas Woodhouse.
And his boy didn’t
like that one bit.
So what happened?
George got the goods on him.
On video.
Played the tape one Sunday
night at a family dinner
I would have paid
money to be present at.
George torched Daddy’s marriage
and his career at the same time.
Who will ever hire a field op
who’s bested by his own kid?
I don’t like liars.
You are so rock and roll.
That must have been
deeply traumatic.
How old were you?
Thirty-seven.
Oh.
Did your father not know
what you do for a living?
Oh, no, he knew.
Thomas just thought
he was very good.
George was better.
I hear you’ve never been
beaten in the chair.
You’re like some kind of legend.
Is it true? No one
can lie to you?
Better not to find out.
Well, when are you
gonna poly me, George?
Sorry.
Of course, what came after
can hardly be blamed on George.
I think that’s enough.
The man had been
depressed for 30 years.
Freddie, it ends.
- Right now.
- Shut the fuck up
when you talk to
people, Freddie.
I have a game.
We go around the table and
each of us makes a resolution.
The way you might at New Year.
Some personal issue that
needs to be addressed.
"I resolve to quit
smoking," for example.
Oh, this is some
groundbreaking shit, George.
But we don’t make the
resolution for ourselves.
We make it for the
person to our right.
I’m not sure that’s a good idea.
I’m certain it’s a terrible one.
Are you joking?
I don’t believe he is.
- I’m in.
- I’m getting another bottle.
This is a new one.
Brand-new.
Well, I wasn’t aware the
agency would track that,
but I’ll, um... I’ll
keep it in mind.
Thank you, George.
So, when you say
"erotic fiction..."
Leave the poor woman alone.
I don’t need defending.
I like a dirty story.
It’s not a crime.
I believe it’s my turn.
Yeah?
Okay.
"I resolve to..."
Wait, I’m speaking
in his voice, yeah?
Okay.
"I resolve to do my best
to finish second
whenever possible."
Or once, even.
Once would be a
refreshing change of pace.
- Sing it, sister.
- Trust me,
one day, you’ll be
thrilled to finish at all.
You are so full
of shit, Freddie.
Note taken. You’ll be
begging me to stop.
Oh, what every woman longs for.
An endless, abrasive experience.
Let’s move on.
My turn.
This one’s for you, right?
Okay.
"I resolve to figure out
this old man obsession of mine."
Oh.
I figured that one out
a long time ago, hon.
Young men bore the
shit out of me.
I mean, you, you know,
you haven’t done anything.
You haven’t been anywhere.
All you want to do
is invite me over to watch
you play video games.
Oh, God.
Did I get that one right?
Second date:
Call of Duty: Pacific Theater.
Well, this has been
- absolutely delightful.
- I may be old
and wizened, but at least I know
how to book a decent
restaurant, Major.
- It’s Colonel.
- Colonel Xbox.
- Okay.
- Major Minecraft.
Fucking hilarious shit, mate.
Promise you’ll go down on
him while he plays Zelda
so he can die a happy
little soldier, won’t you?
Shut the fuck up, Freddie.
What is your problem tonight?
You know, the real
problem with old men
is the miserable,
suffocating fear of death.
I mean, it’s there, so...
so they can feel it,
and they are quite literally
pissing themselves with fear,
which I-I suppose explains
their pathetic, priapic
lunging at anything that moves.
I’m wondering if perhaps
you’ve had enough to drink.
But it’s my turn now, right?
I get to speak for
Freddie now, right?
"I’m gonna stop fucking her."
Well, I’m afraid
I can’t, gorgeous.
I am powerless before you.
Not me.
Her.
Is this some sort of prank?
This is why you
can’t date SIGINT.
They’re all fucking insane.
It would appear...
it would appear my young
friend and I might benefit
from a private conversation.
I’m not going anywhere.
I am...
You know, maybe on
Monday, the two of you
could find a few minutes
to come by my office.
We could sit down and then...
- I’m not going anywhere.
- My God, you are an infant.
- It’s not the issue.
- You’re psychotic.
Pathological.
I have indulged your
constant need for support
and encouragement
and reassurance
and fucking paternal engagement
for a year and a half now,
and I’m sick to
fucking death of it.
He left.
I’m so sorry Daddy
walked out the door,
probably because he
didn’t love Mummy,
but maybe because he
became so hopelessly bored
with your needy,
constant demands
that he figured
getting out was better!
And that is a shitting
tragedy, but it happens.
It happens, and you move on!
That’s what a healthy
human being does.
You are a perversion of what
a man is supposed to be.
- Stop it.
- You are a diseased creature
who has spent the last
20 years of her life
running in frantic circles,
trying to compensate
for a so-called tragedy
that is quite possibly
the most boring story ever told,
and I’ve had it with you.
I hate you. I hate
you so fucking much!
I have slept with no one but you
for the past year and a half,
you sweet fucking lunatic!
No one!
And, my God, how
I regret it now.
Get some help!
And stop spraying your
sickness on the rest of us,
on the loyal,
faithful, decent men
who have only tried to love you
as well and as truly
as they possibly could.
The Zetter Hotel in Clerkenwell.
I beg your pardon?
That’s the hotel you prefer.
Normally, Mondays and Thursdays,
easiest for you because
it’s the department meetings
and you can slip away.
Your lover pays with a
credit card in her own name.
I assume you split it in
cash, but that’s immaterial.
As is her name.
The junior suite with city
view is your favorite.
I don’t like liars.
Fucking hell! Wait,
don’t move it.
Don’t move it. Don’t
fucking move it!
Okay, I got it. I
got it. I got it.
That is the most boring
thing you’ve ever done.
- Hands down.
- Stay still. Stay still.
Look at me. Look at me.
All right, I’ll swap you.
- Okay.
- Give me the arm.
I wonder if it’s possible
you went just a bit heavy
on the DZM 5.
I may well have.
Did you see what
you needed to see?
I don’t know yet.
That was the rock. Now
I watch the ripples.
Leave the rest.
I will.
Just give me two minutes.
Leave it.
I will.
What does it do?
What does what do?
Severus.
I’m afraid that’s
in the black bag.
Want me to guess?
No.
Dirty tricks, malware, meant
to disable a government.
Why would you say that?
Hmm? Oh, Severus Alexander.
You know, the Roman
emperor whose, uh...
uh, assassination led to
50 years of civil war.
If you like.
You know what I like. Hurry up.
George.
Sorry.
Come here.
If you were in a situation,
if you needed my help...
I do need your help.
Scratch my back.
- Wouldn’t matter what it was...
- Please stop talking.
I would do anything for you.
Would you?
Yes.
Anything at all?
Would you lie?
Yes. But never to you.
That’s sweet.
Would you lie to me?
Only if I had to.
- Would you kill for me, George?
- Yes.
- Would you?
I’m going to bed.
What’s wrong?
Nothing.
Maybe this weekend?
Someplace nice.
Don’t stay up too late.
The fuck?
Wait, wait, wait.
Phil? Phil?
I thought maybe a
movie this week.
Uh, I’m out of the country
Wednesday, back Thursday.
Maybe tomorrow, then.
Sure.
Is anything playing?
I hear Dark Windows is good.
Dark Windows.
Don’t know that one.
Should we see it?
Love to.
Where are you off
to on Wednesday?
Black bag.
Right.
George Woodhouse.
Forgot my badge. Can
I get a temporary?
Proper badge protocol is
essential, Mr. Woodhouse.
Never happen again.
- Great party.
- Glad you could make it.
Fingers still work.
Look, I know she’s
crazy as a fucking loon,
but she makes me happy.
My whole life, all I’ve
done is do for people,
Susan and the kids.
I get nothing but hate for it.
Clarissa expects
exactly nothing.
Okay.
You’ve heard about Meacham?
He’s dead. Coronary.
- When?
- Last night.
- I just saw him.
- People always say that.
Little young for a heart
attack, don’t you think?
Yes.
Do you know what
he was working on?
No.
I need to see Kathryn.
She’s got Stieglitz in
there. You might want to...
...all here, the task at hand,
to fully express those
needs and desire to you
over the last month and a half.
But have I seen it? Do I...
Sorry to interrupt.
Why would your key be in my bag?
Found it on the closet floor
and thought it was yours.
They all look alike.
My bag’s by the desk.
I need my key back by 1:00.
Two minutes.
You okay?
I just heard about Meacham.
Terrible.
Anything else?
No.
Grab yourself something on the
way home, if you don’t mind.
I might stop off at the lake.
Zurich?
47.3701 north,
8.5411 east.
Sorry. Running behind.
Mm-hmm.
Can you go a few minutes late?
If we don’t do 45, I
can’t clear the mandate.
Uh, I make that 2:06.
Fine.
Uh, sleep remains inconsistent.
I take two-point-five to
three milligrams of lorazepam,
the first at 8:00,
the second at 11:00
and the third in the night.
After the first nightmare.
You’re still having
them every night?
Yes.
Um... the herbal sleep aids
leave me groggy, so
I-I discontinued,
and zolpidem is at most
an every-other-day option.
More than point-five
milligrams two days in a row
produces unmotivated
rage the next morning.
And three or more
days in a row...
...things get even uglier.
What?
I just... I-I think that’s
an extremely careful report.
How so?
Uh, lorazepam three
milligrams or below,
zolpidem below 20
milligrams per month,
and the herbal, that’s...
that’s ashwagandha, right?
- Yes.
- Yeah. Yeah.
I think those
amounts and dosages
are just under my
reporting requirements.
And you know that.
And you feel it’s duplicitous
for me to want to avoid
involvement in psych
services reporting chains?
As I said, I-I
think it’s careful.
I’m the head of sig ops;
of course I’m careful.
Well, that’s not
the goal in here.
The goal is to
satisfy the mandate
so I can get back to work.
Why on earth are you sleeping
with Ramrod Jimmy Stokes?
- He’s beneath you.
- Let’s keep this professional.
Professional?
You came to my home.
You drank, you ate, you
talked about your sex life.
What in God’s name is
professional about that?
Maybe it was an
observational visit.
I’ve had it up to my eyeballs
being watched by every
single person around me.
Oh, yes, by all means,
write that one down.
Paranoid ideations.
Buy me another
mandatory six months.
You know, I always know
when you’re arriving.
Because the aroma of hostility
wafts in ahead of you.
Oh, well, that’s the first
interesting thing you’ve said.
How are things with George?
The other day, Arthur
Stieglitz told me
that my devotion to my marriage
is my professional weakness.
That my feelings for
George are a gaping wound
through which any
idiot can attack me.
He told me I want too much
and that I cannot have it all.
I’m going to have his job.
You watch.
Is he right?
If a situation presents itself,
would you choose your
marriage over everything else?
I value loyalty.
To what?
You were raised
Catholic, weren’t you?
Hmm? Mm.
Never mind. You were.
12 years at St.
Anthony’s in Blackpool.
Yeah. Did they tell you
you were a bad little girl?
Oh, is that why
you like erotica?
Because it’s naughty.
It’s against the rules.
Says everything you can’t.
Yeah. Oh, I bet you go
for dirty talk, too.
I’ll report you
completed the session.
- You can go.
- Why?
This is just getting good.
Zoe Vaughan, nice Catholic
girl from the North,
just wants to help people,
wants to talk about
their problems.
Come on. Why us?
I’m curious about people.
And right now, I’m
curious about you.
Zolpidem.
After three days, you said
"things get even uglier."
- I get moods.
- What kind of moods?
- Dark.
- Suicidal?
No.
Panicked.
Over money still?
Despite all evidence
to the contrary?
Well, I’ll not end
up like my mother.
That’s the first interesting
thing you’ve said.
If Severus is
deployed as intended,
thousands of innocent
people will die.
When are you gonna
poly me, George?
Shit.
Sorry.
I know I’m intruding.
A situation’s come
up that I think falls
outside our usual
reporting parameters.
If you prefer, we
could use a SCIF.
Go on.
- It’s awkward.
- Preamble noted.
Our financial people have
been working with HMRC,
running a sweep of banks
in tax haven countries.
They routinely run
ID scrapes past us
for non-insignificant balances,
in case one of our
persona IDs is used
to open an offshore account.
Never once has been.
This time, they got a hit.
What’s the fake name?
"Margaret Langford."
DOB and name match an
SIS-generated passport
from 2008.
- Who registered it?
- Scrubbed in ’09.
Search old case files for
the name and date of birth.
Also scrubbed. She’s
a nonentity post-2009.
- Thumbprint?
- None required.
It was just before Phase II.
What bank holds the account?
Asia Trust & Capital.
Obscure choice. It’s
what I would’ve picked.
Facial rec on surveillance
cams outside the bank
the day the account was opened.
That was eight months ago,
and Myanmar’s non-co-op.
Sometimes if you
know who to ask...
If it’s Myanmar, how do we
know about the account at all?
Well, somebody got jumpy
and transferred the money
out of there when it looked
like there’d be another coup.
We got a hit on the incoming
SWIFT at the new bank.
- Where?
- Raffenkalt/Suisse AG.
Zurich.
Zurich?
That mean something?
How much is in the account?
Seven million.
Pounds.
So one of our people
stole a straw man identity
and has been paid seven
million pounds under it.
Yes.
What?
"Margaret Langford" was
used a handful of times
by a SIGINT op in 2008
before discontinuance.
Used by whom?
Your wife.
I see.
As I said, I thought this was
outside our normal
reporting parameters.
- Who else knows?
- No one.
Leave it with me, please.
James.
Was the money deposited
in increments or lump sum?
Lump sum.
Someone sold something
extremely valuable.
Alice?
Alice, are you here?
Richard, what are you doing?!
What? I just opened the door.
- Where’s Monica?
- She’s gone to get help.
You should’ve heard yourself.
I hate birds.
Give me the torch.
I like the torch.
Use your phone.
Trout?
- Vendace.
- Oh.
- Been saving it.
- Delicious.
Is it a difficult catch?
Next to impossible.
When will you be back?
Oh, tomorrow, late.
Don’t wait up.
I hate the distance.
Well, we’re pretty good at it.
It seems grotesque.
What’s asked of a person.
Oh, shit.
Bon voyage.
Or Gute Reise.
Love you.
♪ To love, to love, to love ♪
Shit.
♪ Oh, how lucky we are... ♪
What the fuck, George?!
Am I in trouble?
Not at all.
So what’s up, man?
I understand, uh, you and
Freddie are still together.
Yeah.
Isn’t that a bit awkward?
Because I pinned his hand to
the table with a steak knife?
That comes to mind.
He forgave me. I forgave him.
You know? The hand thing
kind of evened us out.
Okay.
George, you come to my
apartment at 11:00 at night
asking about my relationship.
I’m not shocked, and I’m
not even sure I’m saying no,
but are you actually doing this?
Uh, no.
Then what do you want?
You have MOD imagery
oversight in Building 321
on one of the 64 eyes.
For a minute there, I
thought you were human.
I need a brief Keyhole
redirect tomorrow morning,
and it needs to be
un-logged and unrecorded.
I don’t even think
that’s possible.
It is.
There are brief periods
between satlink handovers
where a satellite could be
used for another purpose
without detection.
I’ve done it, in Ratcliffe.
But this one has
to be unofficial.
Why would I do
something like that?
I would consider
myself in your debt.
What does that get me?
Privacy.
I have personally never found
ecstasy use to be a
compromising factor.
But combined with multiple
sexual partners...
...it would be of
issue, to Freddie.
His infidelity is one
thing, but yours...
Freddie’s old-fashioned.
- You’re a bastard.
- It’s important.
What if I love him?
Then you’ll help me.
But does that matter to you?
You know, the human part.
Does that... do you
care about that?
Who am I supposed to be with?
Tell me.
Sorry, uh, it seemed rhetorical.
I can’t date outside.
They don’t understand.
And I can’t date inside because
we’re all fucking liars.
You know, professional ones
with a perfect
excuse every time.
"Well, where were
you last week?"
"Black bag."
"What did you do on
Friday?" "Black bag."
When you can lie
about everything,
when you can deny everything,
how do you tell the
truth about anything?
How does that work?
How can that possibly work?
I don’t know.
But you do know.
You do know because
it works for you.
And you’re the perfect
fucking couple,
and everyone knows
it, so tell me.
Tell me how it works.
6:30 a.m. tomorrow.
A few minutes early to be safe.
Is there a secure view site?
There’s a lookdown
SCIF off the main 64.
Good.
Thank you for the wine.
You didn’t have to come
at me like that, you know.
I would’ve done
it for you anyway.
Ready for some treason?
That isn’t funny.
Sure it is.
Where are we looking?
47.3701 north,
8.5411 east.
Okay. There’s only
one good option there.
Very masculine Milstar
satellite up at 938 miles.
Ops arc isn’t used much.
It’s over Liechtenstein.
It’s that one. Second row
down, third from the right.
About to hand off to a Gaofen-4.
How long will we have?
Three minutes, 20 seconds.
Does he miss anything?
The major? Never once.
Ready?
- Wait.
- George.
No, George, I’m naked out
here. Are we doing this or not?
Go.
Handoff.
Zurich? What the
hell’s in Zurich?
Move in.
Closer. Same coordinates.
Closer.
Nice bench. Are we done?
Wait.
They’re late.
You are one naughty
husband, George.
You asked how it works.
To be with someone
in this business.
This is how.
You each know what you know,
and you know what you’ll do,
and you never discuss
certain things again.
I watch her. I assume
she watches me.
If she’s in trouble,
even of her own making,
I will do everything in
my power to extricate her.
No matter what that means.
You understand?
My God, that’s so hot.
That’s how it works.
It’s the only way.
Can you get any closer?
Facial rec?
Nothing?
Give it a minute.
Kulikov.
- One minute.
- Hang on.
Trying something.
It’s a lipreading AI.
Still in beta.
Audio coming.
The money’s in place.
Do your fucking job,
and I’ll release.
She isn’t selling.
She’s buying.
It’s a complicated situation.
14 seconds.
You need to think about it.
- Get them back.
- Yeah, trying.
- I’ve got to let them go.
- Get them back!
I’ve got to let them go!
- Shit.
- What?
It’s not responding.
- Get rid of it.
- I don’t know what...
I’m trying. I...
Why the...
Shit!
Did he see?
I don’t know. Did you record?
It’s automatic.
Go into the root
files and delete.
Keystroke logs, too.
Yeah, well, I hope you
got what you wanted.
If I’m going down,
you’re coming with me.
I’ll keep that in mind.
I don’t understand.
Which part?
All of it.
James, come on. How old are you?
Come over here.
What?
It’s not that kind of visit.
What kind of visit is it, then?
The kind where I say we’re
not seeing each other anymore.
And why not again?
Because I don’t want to.
What about the times we had our
little sessions, over there?
- You wanted to then.
- Yeah.
And now I don’t.
You see, this isn’t normal.
The way you’re doing
this, just so you know.
And what we did in here...
None of this is normal.
No, it isn’t.
You’re as sick as your patients.
Possibly.
But there’s no law that says
that therapists can’t
have issues of their own.
- Are you seeing someone else?
- Yes.
Fuck me, you’re cold.
Yeah, a bit.
Yeah, you’re even cold about
whether or not you’re cold.
I’m gonna clear your
mandate permanently.
I’ll tell psych services
to recommend a psychiatrist
for any prescriptive issues
you might have in the future.
I told you things.
All your thoughts and
feelings are confidential.
Our relationship can just...
Yeah, I don’t give a shit
about the relationship.
I’m over it. I got something
else on the side, too.
I told you operational things.
Are you referring to Severus?
I was drunk as hell.
Anything you told me regarding
Severus is also privileged.
That’s great.
’Cause it’d be a real
drag to have to kill you.
I’ve never appreciated
that sort of humor.
Yeah, and I never liked
that about you either.
You know what you
could use in here?
A velvet Jesus with
eyes that follow you.
You’d like that, wouldn’t you?
It’s duty desk.
Go ahead.
Thanks, Mom.
Yes?
When?
How long?
I’ll be right there.
I got to go.
I left some things
at your place.
They’re in a pouch at
the desk under your name.
I left it there this morning.
This is the best
breakup I ever had.
Seriously, I enjoyed myself.
Take care, Zoe.
You’re a fucking piece of work.
The major called.
We’ve got a breach.
It’s me. Don’t be
a dick. Come on.
Jesus.
You’ll want to know about this.
Oh, no, no, no.
All right.
Let’s get started.
Ms. Childs, would you please?
Okay, so this is
Vadim Pavlichuk,
the dissident Russian
general under house arrest
in Liechtenstein for
the past six months.
Pavlichuk’s been known to
be working with a network
of exiled militarists for the
overthrow of the Russian regime
due to its mismanagement
of the war.
We’ve had the house on lockdown
for 24 hours since he arrived.
If Pavlichuk made a move,
we wanted to know first.
He has now made a move.
These are the heat signatures
in the house at 6:31 a.m.
Central European Time.
Seven unique sigs.
We then lost signal
with the house
during a routine satlink
handover for about...
- Three minutes, 20 seconds.
- Thank you.
Three minutes, 20 seconds.
When we regained signal and
ran thermals again at 6:35,
this is what we see.
There are now only five.
For the last two hours,
we’ve been accounting for
all the individual sigs.
We got all five as
they came and went.
None of them were Pavlichuk.
So the son of a
bitch is out, hmm?
How could that happen?
How would he know the exact
timing of a satlink handover?
Well, fucking exactly.
How could he know unless
someone here told him?
We look away, he takes off.
It was an operation.
Very precise.
Hmm?
There is a stranger
in our house.
Have we picked up
Pavlichuk since he left?
He’s good.
He’s hunched over in
a black van somewhere,
off to malefact.
Uh, well, our assumption is
that his right-hand former
lieutenant Andrei Kulikov
is en route to pick him up now.
Their intentions are unclear.
Kulikov had a meeting with
an unknown party in Zurich
this morning, so we’re
waiting on visuals for that.
Mm-hmm. Keep at it.
Should we...
Should we notify CIA?
Oh, fuck them.
I’m sick of being treated
like an ATM for intel.
And I’m certainly not showing
them our dirty linens.
If there’s a traitor
in the house,
I want to know who
it is before they do.
This stays in the room.
You said the major was, uh...
...aware of the redirect?
Yes. I got a signal
alert and called him.
- He already knew.
- Hmm.
Have him reassigned...
somewhere lovely, the Bahamas.
Tell him it’s a promotion,
effective immediately.
He travels tomorrow.
Can I ask, strategically,
why do we care that
Pavlichuk is out?
S-6 and below, please clear.
Severus.
We believe Pavlichuk has
been given a physical copy.
That’s why we watched him.
If Kulikov manages to get
him back into Moscow with it,
well...
Mr. Smalls, educate
our colleagues.
Severus is a Stuxnet polymorph
we developed with NSA.
It has to be
physically introduced
to a nuclear reactor
to get past an air gap.
But once it’s in, it can target
and melt down the reactor core.
It was a CYBERCOM op.
Why the fuck would we make that?
Theoreticals. Capabilities.
It shouldn’t have
left the building.
And we realized, if
we can do it to them,
- once the thing is out there...
- They can do it to us.
It was a good idea.
Hmm?
A meltdown would
cause political havoc.
For an enemy involved
in an endless war
and a teetering government,
they’d run dear leader
out of Moscow on a rail.
We’d be rid of the
prick once and for all.
We didn’t do it...
...but it was a damn good idea.
It would appear someone
here felt the same way.
Mm-hmm. And redirected the eye
so Pavlichuk could
escape with the drive.
He’s on his way to Russia
now to initiate a meltdown,
and it’ll be our goddamn fault!
Find the leak.
Methods won’t be questioned.
This can’t be good.
It isn’t.
George ordered the redirect.
I helped him do it.
Thanks.
Kathryn.
Jesus, Freddie.
Got a minute?
Does anyone else know?
No.
- Can you trust Clarissa?
- Not particularly.
- To keep it to herself, I mean.
- I think so.
She’s fond of George.
She’s concerned.
Whatever operation he’s running,
he’s in a very leaky boat.
If Pavlichuk gets back
to Russia, it’s on him.
He’d get 35 years.
Is there anything you can do?
How was Zurich?
It was pointless.
He had nothing.
I don’t know why I was there.
I spent the rest of the day
chasing down Gunther at FIS,
but he was useless.
Do you have any idea why
George would be watching you?
None whatsoever.
All right.
You be ready in the morning.
I need a night to think.
Okay.
Just you and me.
Yes?
Of course.
I believe I’ve been set up.
I think I have been, too.
By Freddie, of all people.
Why?
Well, he’s playing me.
He thinks I’ll take
action to protect you.
And he’s right.
I will kill for you, George.
You know that.
Freddie stole Severus.
Ah, maybe, maybe not.
It’s not really about
that anymore, is it?
Somehow it’s...
...it’s about us.
There’s a plan.
And a counterplan.
One is using you to get to me,
the other, me to get to you.
Well, what are we
going to do about that?
Disrupt.
All of it.
Bait someone into
an overreaction.
Will there be another
mess to clean up?
Only if we do it right.
Wish you’d called sooner. I
didn’t really have any gear.
Hop in.
Fishing’s not really my thing.
Patience. All you need.
We’ll be back in plenty of time.
It’s easier to think out here.
I need something.
Geofencing on Andrei Kulikov.
Last known is Zurich.
I want a moving
trace on his cell,
and I want it to be un-logged.
I’m not going to
prison for you psychos.
Oh, you’re too far in
to worry about that now,
don’t you think?
Fucking made for each other.
I’d like to set up a
series of polygraphs.
Today.
The usual room at Vauxhall.
Who did you have in mind?
Freddie Smalls.
Clarissa Dubose.
Dr. Zoe Vaughan.
Why her?
Freddie saw her twice a week
for the past eight months.
Leakage.
And I’ve seen her, too.
I know. Put yourself
down as well.
Transparency.
Anyone else?
Not for the moment.
So, that Swiss banking issue.
I’d been meaning to
follow up with you.
Of course one’s mind
goes to a possible
Severus connection.
That had occurred to me.
Had it?
It would appear to be linked.
Have you shared your
suspicions with anyone else?
Of course not.
But you still feel
certain of the identity
of the person who opened
the offshore account?
No.
No, that’s the thing.
That’s why I’d been meaning
to follow up with you.
Oh.
"Margaret Langford."
The passport name that
Kathryn used in ’08.
Turns out there was
some sort of glitch.
It was repeatedly
recycled by the system,
passed around SIS for a decade.
There’s at least a dozen uses.
40 or 50 border records.
Seems odd you’d miss that.
Yes.
Yeah, I’m kicking myself.
It was sloppy.
The point is...
it could’ve been anyone.
We’re no longer
looking at Kathryn.
"We"?
You and me.
Whoa, whoa! Wh-What do I do?
Let him run for a minute.
Americano for Emma.
Thank you.
Live cell zone lock.
That’s the trace log-in.
He’s moving.
What is this, my birthday?
Can you get it approved quickly?
To keep Severus
from getting out?
Speed of light.
I’ll owe you.
Really, why do you care?
It’s a private agenda.
That’s not really an answer.
One of our people
is compromised.
Drone strike resets everything.
Just Kulikov or am I taking
anybody else out with him?
It’s a gift from fucking heaven.
- Do you want it or not?
- Yes, we want it.
I’m just getting my
arms around the global.
He’s traveling across Poland
for the next three hours.
Don’t wait.
This is ikizukuri.
Thank you, Jimmy.
What do you want? Hmm?
Ikizukuri is illegal in the U.K.
If you don’t mind, I
prefer to eat alone.
You know, I can’t
see all the corners,
but I can tell the shape.
And this, all yours.
What could you possibly
be talking about?
Oh, please.
Your operation stops.
Right now.
Mm.
You’re a little late for that.
- Yeah?
- Mm.
Ask for the CIA drone
logs when you get back.
How many would a
meltdown have killed?
10,000? 20,000?
What did you do?
Hmm?
Canceled your op.
You stupid son of a bitch.
You cannot imagine the
damage you just did.
Mm?
Now, I don’t know who
you enlisted to help,
but George has got
his teeth in it now.
- Mm.
- Have you seen him
when his jaws lock on something?
You’ll rip yourself apart
before he’ll let go.
Eat up.
This ends with someone
in the boot of a car.
If we could make this quick.
- Shall we?
- Be my guest.
Is today Friday?
Yes.
Do you reside in
the United Kingdom?
Yes.
Is Frederick Alan Smalls
your true legal name?
Yes.
Did you masturbate this morning?
Oh, good.
The embarrassing personal
questions start early.
Yes or no whenever
possible, please.
You know, I’ve been
looking forward to this.
Did you masturbate this morning?
No.
Didn’t have time.
Are you sitting down?
Yes.
Are the lights on in this room?
Are you now in the
City of Westminster?
No.
Do you enjoy toast?
Very much.
Yes or no.
Yes.
Have you ever physically
assaulted a significant other
during an argument?
Girl, you know I have.
Again, yes or no.
Yes.
Enthusiastically.
Do you wear contact lenses?
Yes.
Do you smoke cigarettes?
No.
Are you seated at the moment?
Yes.
Is it morning or afternoon?
Afternoon. Can we
go back to the EPQs?
They’re more fun.
Is your mother’s name Quiana?
Yes.
When did you first
become aware of Severus?
What’s Severus?
Have you ever failed to
support any child of yours?
Uh...
only emotionally.
Yes or no.
Yes.
Were you resentful that I
passed you over for the CI job?
- I’m fucking human.
- Yes or no.
Were you resentful that I
passed you over for the job?
Yes.
Did you steal Severus as
a means of getting even?
No.
When did you first
become aware of Severus?
About two months ago.
How did you become aware?
Professional
restrictions prevent me
from answering the question.
How did you become aware?
Same answer.
Did a patient divulge
the information to you?
Same answer.
Outside of war,
have you ever killed
another person?
Define "war."
Declared or undeclared conflict
between the United Kingdom
and another country
or non-state actor.
No.
Outside of war,
have you ever been
in a shooting, knifing or fight
where someone was
seriously injured?
Yes.
Have you ever
betrayed your country?
No.
What is your relationship
with Dr. Zoe Vaughan?
Patient and social acquaintance.
Would you like to take a break?
I’m good.
Is your middle name Beatrice?
No.
Please answer the
question truthfully.
Is your middle name Beatrice?
Yeah.
Are you tightening your anal
sphincter muscle right now?
Yes.
Have you read Physiological
Stress Response
and Polygraph Deception
by Weymouth and Coombs?
Cover to cover.
Yes or no.
Yes.
Will you please release
your sphincter muscle?
Sure thing, George.
Who asked you to
plant the movie stub
in the wastebasket in my closet?
What?
No one.
How many people are you
personally connected with
who were aware of Severus?
That question is
inappropriately operational.
How many people are
you personally...
George, you’re CI. You
know I can’t answer that.
Did you steal Severus?
No.
Did you steal Severus for money?
Did you steal
Severus for ideology?
What ideology?
Did you steal Severus
because of your ideology?
The question assumes
I stole Severus.
True or false: There is no God.
False.
How many sexual partners
have you had in the
last three months?
Two.
True or false:
The greater good outweighs
immediate legal
or ethical limits.
Impossible to answer
without specifics.
Do you think you’re
smarter than most people?
Georgie, I know I am.
Yes or no.
Yes.
Would you like to
come for dinner
at our home tomorrow evening?
Huh?
I need your help individually
to figure something out.
Can you come?
Um...
Yeah, sure.
Well, I had so
much fun last time.
Yes or no.
Is this an order?
We’ll expect you at 8:00.
Wait, what the fuck
did we just learn here?
See you tomorrow.
You okay?
Just nerves.
Only one thing left to learn.
Will it go there?
That’s what scares me.
It should.
I haven’t had this
much fun in years.
What’s with the
command performance?
Come in.
Work or social?
Yes.
I thought it was just me.
We all did.
So where’s this fucking dinner?
- I didn’t cook.
- We have a game.
Ah, shit. Really?
I don’t think I’m willing
to submit to this.
And here’s how it works.
We go around the table
and George will ask each
one of you a question.
And if you get it
wrong, you lose.
This is inappropriate.
And the loser
doesn’t get up from the table.
- For fuck’s sake.
- Are you out of your mind?
The two of you, I swear to God.
- I’m leaving.
- Sit down.
You are cordially
invited to an evening
of fun and games with
George and Kathryn.
That’s a new rug.
Anyone who’d prefer to
answer the questions
in front of an OSRAC
committee is free to go.
Why is there a new rug?
You’re disturbed. All of
you. Do you realize that?
You’re sick!
I mean, you just fuck
each other, literally,
and back and forth
and back and forth.
Is there one normal person
inside that entire
fucking building?
Fine!
I’ve got nothing to hide.
Then we’ll start with you.
When did you first
sleep with Freddie?
Oh, that’s just gross.
Sick.
My apologies.
That was ungentlemanly
but necessary.
Dr. Vaughan is the woman
Freddie’s been meeting
at the Zetter Hotel
in Clerkenwell.
You motherfucker.
Seven or eight weeks ago.
- Thank you.
- Is that a joke?
With him? Why?
Manipulation.
She thought she’d need
something from him eventually.
Ah, come on. Don’t be a prick.
Isn’t it just possible...
No, it isn’t.
He’s right.
After the redirect
was discovered,
you alerted
Dr. Vaughan, didn’t you?
Yes, that’s right.
You’ll want to know about this.
I need you to do something.
I am putty in your
hands. What is it?
So, you told me
about the redirect,
knowing that I would take
action to cover for George.
He’s traveling across Poland
for the next three hours.
Don’t wait.
Yes.
Clarissa.
What the fuck do you want?
Only to congratulate you.
You’re the best manipulator of
the polygraph I’ve ever seen.
- I didn’t lie.
- I know.
You didn’t need to.
You had nothing to
do with any of it.
Was it your idea to plant the
movie ticket so I’d find it
or someone else’s?
What movie ticket?
Did catch my eye.
Not so hard to do,
given my profession.
The hell are you
talking about, George?
Was Stieglitz the one who
came to you with the idea
of stealing Severus?
That would make the most sense.
To destabilize Moscow,
to implicate Kathryn,
who threatened Stieglitz, and
to move me out of your way.
Three birds, one stone.
Somehow, you removed
the Severus malware
from the building.
But you got excited
about your plan,
you drank too much and
told Dr. Vaughan about it.
What you didn’t know
is how profound her
religious beliefs are.
You’re turning on me
to cover up your own
treasonous actions.
The kind of beliefs that
would not permit her
to allow the deaths of tens
of thousands in a meltdown.
This is a fantasy.
This is all one of
his fucking fantasies.
It’s why I had a
hard time at first.
It wasn’t one plan,
you see, it was two.
Separate but interlocking.
Working for and
against each other.
You manipulated me so
Pavlichuk could escape.
And you and Freddie did
the same with Kathryn
so she would have him
killed to bail me out.
Causa et effectus.
Isn’t that right?
You two make it almost easy.
The only thing you give a
shit about is each other.
For the record, I knew.
I did it anyway because
it needed doing.
And you had me lured to Zurich.
I thought I was
buying back Severus,
but you made it look
like I was selling.
You opened the account
in Myanmar yourself,
didn’t you?
This is all conjecture.
Turns out
Myanmar does cooperate.
You just have to
know who to ask.
Razman still owes me.
Severus was a good plan.
I’d do it again, ten
times out of ten.
It was a decent frame,
and it would have
ended the fucking war!
It was right, it was
brave, and it was noble.
Which one was the reason
you killed Meacham?
Because it was right or
because it was noble?
Because it was necessary.
I never told you all
the name of the game.
What’s the game, Kathryn?
"See Who Picks Up the Gun."
For fuck’s sake.
Come on, George.
What? You take me
out in handcuffs,
you say your bit, I
say mine, then what?
You still go down.
Maybe she doesn’t, but you will.
You got nothing... nothing hard.
You got suspicions,
hearsay and pillow talk.
And, you know, your
recorded confession.
Shall we discuss the
terms of your surrender?
You’re bluffing.
You should’ve killed
me on the boat, George.
Now, I don’t mind
what you two did.
You saved lives.
But don’t ever fuck
with my marriage again.
Okay.
Freddie. Table.
Darling, we need the rug.
Ninth floor.
Doors opening.
Lift going down.
Doors closing.
Terrible about Stokes.
- So strange.
- Mm.
Disappearing like that.
It’s a very dangerous
line of work.
Mm, I’ll say.
Given all you’ve accomplished,
maybe it’s time to consider
stepping away, Arthur.
Feet first.
Second floor.
Doors opening.
Any way you like.
Lift going down.
He’s completely rattled.
Fantastic.
He won’t be able to
sleep for a whole month.
He wasn’t rattled.
He took credit for
the whole thing.
The CIA is lap
dancing all over him.
It’s a fiction.
He won’t be able to
keep it up forever.
And Stieglitz bores me.
Let’s... let’s talk about you.
Why didn’t you just ask
me about the movie ticket?
Hmm? See if I was lying?
Faith.
You’d never be that sloppy.
A movie stub. Please.
Well, exactly.
It’s almost insulting.
- I knew you’d never lie to me.
- Only if I had to.
Obviously.
One thing.
The, uh, seven million pounds
Stokes put into the
Swiss bank account?
Still there.
Oh. Is it?